They took Leningrad, the hero city,
Ленинград город герой взяли
renamed it
переименовали в
St. Petersburg, Stalin turns over in the State Budgetary Institution
санкт-петербург Сталин в ГБУ
Hello, Wow I painted a whole wall with
Здравствуйте Ничего себе Целую стену
Ukrainian varnish. I'm from the city of
покрасил лак Украины Я из города
Khmelnitsk. You're from the city of Khmelnitsk. Where am I from? I'm
Хмельницке Вы откуда я избург
from Ekaterinburg. And I understood
откуда Екатеринбург А понял
Sverdlovsk Ekaterinburg Well,
Свердловск Екатеринбург Ну и
it was Sverdlovsk, Sverdlovsk for as long as I can
Свердловском он был Свердловском сколько
remember, then Yeltsin
помню потом уже Ельцин декоммунизация
did decommunization  Yes, that they renamed it, that
сделали да что его переименовали что
people didn’t like Sverdlovsk, or that it
Свердловск не нравился людям или что он
wasn’t Yekaterinburg. Well, look
был екатеринбургом не Ну вот смотри вы
what year it was
какого года
born in eighty-second in
рождения восемьдесят второго во в я
eighty-first, it was
восемьдесят первого во в во1 он был
Sverdlovsk, that it was renamed
Свердловск что его переименовали в
Yekaterinburg because it used to be
Екатеринбург потому что Раньше он был
Yekaterinburg, and before, well  this is
Екатеринбург так причём раньше ну вот
our history, our Soviet Motherland,
история наша Советская наша Родина
why they renamed it Well, why did they become
почему его переименовали Ну что стали
ashamed of the Soviet past or that I
стесняться советского прошлого или что
can’t understand Why did you rename it
не могу понять А почему вы переименовали
to sverlov that sverlov was from
в сверлов что сверлов был из
Yekaterinburg I have no idea but I have it
Екатеринбурга Я понятия не имею но я име
already happened, this is our history already
вот уже ж было это же наша история уже
had this one  the answer to your question
был себе этот ответ на ваш вопрос
lies in my question sverlov
заключается в моём вопросе сверлов не
was not from ek
был из ек
who Sverdlov was not from
кто Свердлов не был све не был из
Yekaterinburg Lenin was not from Leningrad
Екатеринбурга Ленин не был с Ленинграда
Stalin was not from Stalingrad
Сталин не был со Сталинграда
Lenin Lenin was associated with Leningrad Kirov
Ленин Ленин был связан с ленинградом
was not Kirov was not in Kirov
Киров не был Киров не был в Кирове
Gorky was not in  Gorky Clearly, you just
Горький не был в горькой Ясно вы просто
don’t, well, you’re a big star, like you’re
которы не ну вы звезда бол типа Вы
really starting. I just asked
реально начинаете Я просто спросил
why you asked, I answered you. Well,
почему вы спросили я вам ответил Ну
look, you don’t
смотрите у вас получается не
respect our Soviet history, you
уважает нашу Советскую историю вы
asked, I m I I’m clarifying that you’re so
спросили я м я я Уточняю что вы так
nervous. I just asked about your
нервничаете Я просто спросил про ваше
name.  of your city Why are you
название вашего города Почему вы
nervous Why did you
нервничаете Почему вы его
rename it Why what happened? I
переименовали Почему что случилось вам
answered you why they renamed it because
ответил почему переименовали потому что
Sverlov was not connected with Yekaterinburg,
сверлов не был связан с екатеринбургом
it’s very simple and why
всё очень просто так а зачем так уже ж
did it already exist? Why rename the
был зачем переименовывать
city I answered your question You’re stupid
города я вам ответил на вопрос Вы тупой
No, so it already existed  Sverdlov
Нет так вот он уже был Свердлов
Sverdlovsk like everyone lived people lived in
Свердловск типа всё жили люди жили в
Sverdlovsk you didn’t care when the
Свердловске пофиг вам было когда
Soviet Union collapsed right away Let’s
Советский Союз развалился сразу Давайте
change Naka
поменяем Нака
under Soviet rule for you it’s not Mulya and
при Советской власти вам это не Муля да
drills like yes And then the gopis Come on
сверлов типа да А потом гопи Давай
Ekaterinburg and that’s it and what what what
Екатеринбург а всё а что что что
Ekaterina built for you And what about the
Екатерина у вас построила А что
communists under  You have everything built by the Soviet regime,
коммунисты при Советской власти у вас
factories built, Yes, and
всё и заводы построенные Да и пароходы
all the steamships. And why didn’t they throw out the factories and
всё И что почему не выкинули заводы да
everything that was not built before the Soviet regime,
все а до Советской власти что не были
if what was built before the Soviet regime had
построе если то что до Советской власти
already rotted a long time ago? But the fact that
уже давным-давно сгнило А вот то что во
during the Soviet regime the
время Советской власти
words were changed to Sverdlovsk  renamed the
слов пере Свердловск переименовали в
schools in Yekaterinburg where children
Екатеринбург школы в которых дети
study children study in schools kindergartens
учатся дети в школах учатся садики
children's factories everything was built by the communists
детские заводы всё построили коммунисты
Which communes have so far been poured out Soviet soz
Какие коммуни пока вылили Советский соз
poured and
перели и
transferred but Leningrad the hero city was taken
пере но Ленинград город герой взяли
renamed to
переименовали в
St. Petersburg Stalin in the State Budgetary Institution
санкт-петербург Сталин в ГБУ
is turning over
переворачивается
stupid Just
дуро Просто
screwed how could this be a city
капец как так можно было был город
Gorky no b Nizhny
горкий нет б Нижний
Novgoro Nizhny Novgorod Stalingrad
новгоро Нижний Новгород Сталинград
was
был
I love the mirror so much If there is a stink to us And why did
Я так люблю зеркаль Коли вони до нас А
you rename the streets You
что вы улиц переименовать Вы то
renamed what you renamed Yes
переименовали что вы то переименовали Да
write to my Telegram directly at once axis VN
пись на мий Telegram прямо зараз ось ВН
apok tse more and more respectfully YouTube Zaga
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube Зага
us through skarg Orcs  in your ban and a
нас через скарг Орки в твый бан и дуже
lot of videos I don’t show people at the moment I don’t
багато видео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about the stream For this
показуе информация про стрими Тому для
purpose, we need to write a Mali operational link
того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
right away, but in the meantime, there’s a telegra
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
okm video, shchezh tsikava and korisna
окм видео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and we’re sorry for you trimati postiyny
информация и мы повинни з вами тримати
operational link regardless  In
постийний оперативный звязок незалежно в
addition, I will show you the process YouTube Glory to
того чи покаже вам проце YouTube Слава
Ukraine
украини
letter
пись
L
L